GINA KENNEDY: Another pose to transition to from your halfway or lunge is a lunge twist.
We're going to have Faith demonstrate that for us right now.
So she's going to come into her halfway lunge.
We're going to have her use her blocks, extending her arms--good--just to make the floor just a little bit more accessible.
Good.
So she's going to curl her back toes under and lift up through her back knee.
Pressing into her heel and squeezing though her thigh.
Good.
She's going to press into her left hand, inhale and rotate her torso towards her knee and reach her right arm up to the sky.
Beautiful.
Now she wants to keep her hips square and keep this knee from flaring out so drawing the knee in.
Good.
Then she presses into that block and reaches up through her fingertips and opens up through her heart and comes into that twist just a little bit deeper.
The whole time engaging this back leg and pressing through her heel.
Good.
Lengthening through the crown of her head.
And then when she's ready, lowering her hand back down to her block and bringing her knee back down.